{
    "id": "44c20d53aebb432a9c3da6bbdd9fafe3",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ran so fast ………………….. he became breathless.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "that",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8d4e51e6d6f4f1f8a8f7b095c83fe2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him ………………….. he was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7c4097a21f604eb1865616d6f85a87fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did ………………….. he was told.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17117c7950b34961b01bbb97c34479b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know ………………… did this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "438e8dfc75824a648e01339c3c73c1b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you are intelligent, you will learn programming in a few weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a00eefb3dd8d404298c62d086767bfe5"
        },
        {
            "question": "People liked him ………………… he was generous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "why"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1387635312774e57a0e6290a61a8036a"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... he was in trouble, I helped him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "As",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65710a4b2d95474fa3f2875129ccea55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mend your ways …………………. it is too late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "when",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70b324677ea84871a461aa9f3c83cfef"
        },
        {
            "question": "He rushed home …………………. he heard the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at once",
                "soon as",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fb1b05de9f7f4108a851f7432038663c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him ………………… old he was.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "how much",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7fcce573f3954af89006fee647a0d618"
        }
    ]
}